[With English subtitles]
[有英文字幕]
[Spy Game]
[间谍游戏]
[Episode 6]
[第6集]
Please take your time.
请慢慢来。
-gentlemen. he. - boss.
-先生。他。- 老板。
[fish leaping]
[鱼跃]
All seafood is delivered here.
海鲜都是送到这里来的。
Ask a worker to get it.
请工人去拿。
To achieve it (dream); to get it (thing.
去实现它（梦想）;去得到它（东西。
OK
好的。
I left the car running.
我让车开着。
please,
请，
Turn off the car for me.
帮我把车关掉。
Ok, no problem.
好的没问题。
Han Jie also kept in touch with her.
韩杰也和她保持着联系。
he is
他是
The supplier of this izakaya.
这家居酒屋的供应商。
This seems like a normal relationship.
这似乎是一种正常的关系。
but everyone
但是每个人
It has something to do with the boss lady.
和老板娘有关系。
Then the situation is not simple.
那么情况可就不简单了。
I have sent someone
我已经派人去
Research her background.
调查她的背景。
Tianyang,
Tianyang,
I have sent you Jiahui's information.
我已经把嘉慧的资料发给你了。
OK
好的。
Zhang Jiahui.
Zhang Jiahui.
[Zhang Jiahui]
[Zhang Jiahui]
Thirty years old.
三十岁了。
Her parents live in Vancouver.
她的父母住在温哥华。
【Education Experience】
【教育经历】
He runs several
他经营着几家
in China.
在中国。
She went to Japan during college,
大学期间她去了日本，
And studied cooking in Japan for many years.
并在日本学习烹饪多年。
She returned to China two years ago,
她两年前回国，
And opened this izakaya.
并开设了这家居酒屋。
She appears to have a clean record.
她似乎有着清白的记录。
Nothing suspicious.
没什么可疑的。
Let's go have another meal. I'll entertain you.
再去吃顿饭吧。我会招待你的。
No.
没有。
Why...
为什么...
Go yourself.
你自己去吧。
What am I going to do?
我要去做什么？
For you who work,
为了工作的你，
By the way, have a meal.
顺便说一句，吃顿饭。
and,
并且，
come to help you
来帮你
Improve your personal emotional intelligence.
提高你的个人情商。
I think
我认为
you should improve
你应该改进
Your IQ.
你的智商。
Sorry, we have to...
抱歉，我们要...
welcome.
欢迎。
Have you closed the door?
你关门了吗？
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Our working hours are irregular.
我们的工作时间不固定。
Here, please.
在这里，请。
Please take a seat.
请坐。
OK, thanks.
好的谢谢。
Prepare a set of cutlery here.
在这里准备一套餐具。
But the chef has gone off duty.
但厨师已经下班了。
I'll cook for you.
我给你做饭。
All right.
好吧。
I want to try your cooking.
我想尝尝你做的菜。
What suggestions do you have?
你有什么建议？
Do you avoid certain foods?
你会避免某些食物吗？
No.
不。
How about the fried pork cutlet rice set meal?
炸猪排饭定食怎么样？
certainly.
当然。
You arrange it.
你安排吧。
OK
好的。
please wait a moment.
请等一会儿。
This is your fried pork cutlet rice.
这是你的炸猪排饭。
Give it a try.
尝尝吧。
how?
如何？
perfect.
完美的。
Why are you here alone today?
今天你怎么一个人在这里？
Myself,
我自己，
You can focus more on the food.
可以更专注于美食。
That makes sense.
这就说得通了。
Have fun.
玩的开心。
Thanks.
谢谢。
This is enough.
这就够了。
I am full.
我饱了。
Won't you have a drink?
你不喝一杯吗？
wine?
葡萄酒？
A little goes a long way.
一点点就可以了。
A bottle of beer!
一瓶啤酒！
Summer limited beers have just arrived.
夏季限定啤酒刚刚到货。
It's perfect for this season.
它非常适合这个季节。
certainly.
当然。
Shall we have a drink?
我们喝一杯吗？
Get an extra glass.
多拿一杯。
how long
多久
Is your restaurant open?
你的餐厅开门了吗？
More than two years.
两年多了。
According to your accent,
根据你的口音，
You don't sound like a local, do you?
你听起来不像当地人，是吗？
My parents are from Jinhai.
我的父母是金海人。
Then they went abroad.
然后他们去了国外。
Now they are old,
如今他们老了，
They really want to come back.
他们真的很想回来。
So I will come back and open a restaurant first
所以我先回来开餐厅
Look how things are going here.
看看这里的情况如何。
Position you selected
您选择的职位
really good.
真的很好。
rent
租金
Not low. correct?
不会低。正确的？
it's good now.
现在好了。
Two years ago,
两年前，
It was not a popular place.
那不是一个受欢迎的地方。
I rented this place
我租了这个地方
Because the rent is low.
因为租金低。
You have a good eye.
你的眼光很好。
There is a company
有公司
and science and technology industrial park.
和科技产业园。
Are they?
他们吗
Do you come here often?
经常来这里吗？
Yes. Often indeed.
是的。确实经常。
What's your signature dish?
你的招牌菜是什么？
There are many types of barbecue food,
烧烤食品的种类有很多种，
Such as grilled fish, grilled skewers,
比如烤鱼、烤串，
and a variety of sashimi.
以及各种生鱼片。
But good sashimi is not common.
但好的生鱼片并不常见。
It depends on fate.
这取决于命运。
Does eating depend on fate?
吃东西要看缘分吗？
certainly.
当然。
Well, I found
嗯，我发现
Supplies from your suppliers
您的供应商的供应
Unstable.
不稳定。
Sashimi
生鱼片
Provided by our suppliers
由我们的供应商提供
It is imported from Norway.
是从挪威进口的。
Actually I often
其实我经常
Go to the seafood market.
去海鲜市场。
but,
但，
I can't tell if this is good or bad.
我无法判断这是好是坏。
Which supplier do you buy from?
您从哪家供应商处购买？
Are you asking me for my secret?
你是在问我的秘密吗？
You noticed.
你注意到了。
It is clear.
很明显。
Let me tell you the truth.
让我告诉你真相。
I got it from another restaurant
我是其他餐厅送来的
Ask about your purchasing channel.
询问您的购买渠道。
Obviously you are not suitable for this profession.
显然你不适合这个职业。
Is it obvious?
很明显吗？
When it comes to ordering food,
说到点餐的时候，
Worse than that girl
比那个女孩还糟糕
Last time I was with you.
上次和你在一起。
Her performance is flawless.
她的表演完美无瑕。
she said
她说的
It’s no different than information.
和信息没有什么不同。
The food is really good.
食物真的很好。
She created a complete image.
她塑造了一个完整的形象。
that's all?
就这样？
That's it for now.
目前为止就这样了。
your meal
你的饭菜
not worth it.
不值得。
Don't say that.
别这么说。
something
有些事
You look nice.
你看起来很好。
It may be useful in the future.
将来可能会有用。
Your emotional intelligence hasn’t improved much.
你的情商并没有提高多少。
You must go again.
你必须再去一次。
Go more often
多去几次吧
it depends.
这取决于。
if you
如果你
find anything,
找到任何东西，
This will definitely waste food.
这肯定会浪费食物。
say.
说话。
habit,
习,
Huang Zicheng logs into the game.
黄子成登录游戏。
knew. I will be right back.
知道了。我马上回来。
password.
密码。
Incorrect!
错误的！
I want to get on that cruise ship.
我想登上那艘游轮。
What is the solution?
有什么办法吗？
I'll add a plugin for you.
我给你添加一个插件。
OK
好的。
Hello. Hello.
你好。你好。
Please take a seat.
请坐。
What mission?
什么使命？
[mistake]
[错误]
Goal F.
目标F。
Carry important confidential documents
携带重要机密文件
Then he fled to Jinhai.
又逃往金海。
Once it falls into the enemy's hands,
一旦落入敌人手中，
The consequences will be disastrous.
后果将不堪设想。
Spies, please go get the documents.
间谍们，请去把文件拿回来。
this mission
这个使命
Sounds simple.
听起来很简单。
[mistake]
[错误]
The second task is not easy.
第二个任务并不容易。
You have to face the real test.
你必须面对真正的考验。
even
甚至
In danger.
在危险之中。
I wish you success.
祝你成功。
Boss Zhang said this task
张老板说这个任务
It could endanger our lives.
可能会危及我们的生命。
Are you afraid?
你怕了吗？
of course not.
当然不是。
I'm not afraid to go to Bangkok
我不怕去曼谷
Let alone return to Jinhai.
更不用说回金海了。
I'm just thinking
我只是在想
Why are there so few clues?
为什么线索这么少
In this mission?
在这个任务中？
There will always be clues.
随时都会有线索。
I'm offline.
我离线了。
Are you not going to play for a while?
你暂时不去玩了吗？
I will be very busy tomorrow.
明天我会很忙。
rest early.
早点休息吧。
The professor's account is encrypted.
教授的帐户是加密的。
In the game,
在游戏里，
He wears a black cloak.
他穿着黑色斗篷。
Hee, it's done.
熙，完成了。
I made a stealth plugin for you.
我给你做了一个隐形插件。
But hurry up.
但快点。
You will be detected at any time.
系统会随时检测到您。
OK
好的。
Yu Xiaoyue was arrested.
于晓月被捕。
Why?
为什么？
no loopholes
没有漏洞
in our actions.
在我们的行动中。
I suspect she was panicking
我怀疑她当时是惊慌失措
and exposed something
并暴露了一些东西
Facing the confidential department.
面对保密部门。
[mistake]
[错误]
Yu Xiaoyue is just a chess piece.
玉小月只是一颗棋子。
Although she was caught,
虽然她被抓了，
We have nothing to lose.
我们不会失去任何东西。
What's the next task?
下一个任务是什么？
[mistake]
[错误]
Is it dangerous to keep moving?
继续移动有危险吗？
I've arranged everything.
我已经安排好了一切。
Someone will help you.
有人会帮助你。
[warn]
[警告]
What's wrong?
怎么了？
There is a plug-in invasion on the cruise ship.
游轮上有插件入侵。
Find it now.
现在就找到它。
[warn]
[警告]
Your room has been hacked.
你的房间被黑客入侵了。
The system is being repaired.
系统正在修复中。
We found a plugin in the system.
我们在系统中找到了一个插件。
We are fixing it.
我们正在修复它。
Retreat now.
现在就撤退吧。
Don't get disconnected inside,
里面不要掉线，
Otherwise your account will be exposed.
否则您的帐户将被暴露。
I did not expect
我没想到
It only took them a minute to find it.
他们只用了一分钟就找到了它。
At least I wasn't killed in vain.
至少我没有白白被杀。
I have a few
我有一些
useful information.
有用的信息。
[Spy Game]
[间谍游戏]
We found the intruder.
我们找到了入侵者。
He is a college student.
他是一名大学生。
He was studying in Jinhai,
他在金海读书，
Just turned 20 years old.
刚满20岁。
Are you sure he is a student?
你确定他是学生？
He did not choose to be resurrected immediately;
他没有选择立即复活，
And he didn't have much money in his wallet.
而且他的钱包里也没有多少钱。
He should be a student.
他应该是一名学生。
[Spy Game]
[间谍游戏]
I still feel
我依然觉得
Possibly disguised.
可能有伪装。
Do you want to check with him?
你想跟他确认一下吗？
[Spy Game]
[间谍游戏]
If he has any questions
如果他有什么问题的话
He will be caught.
他会被抓住的。
OK
好的。
You'd better be careful.
你最好小心一点。
I know.
我知道。
how?
如何？
I heard from stones
我从石头那里听说
You were killed.
你被杀了。
Why?
为什么？
Anger got the better of me.
愤怒战胜了我。
Aren't you awesome?
你不是很厉害吗？
The spy game is their domain.
间谍游戏是他们的领地。
I...
我...
I'm good at playing games.
我擅长玩游戏。
But the interior is difficult to explore.
但内部却很难探究。
Due to a moment of oversight, you have to start over.
由于一时的疏忽，你必须重新开始。
Do you think
你认为
will they find out
他们会发现吗
What is your identity?
你的身份？
Not that easy.
没那么容易。
I have a lot of sock puppets.
我有很多袜子木偶。
【Chinese Police Day】
【中国警察节】
This isn't the first time you've been killed.
这不是你第一次被杀。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
【Chinese Police Day】
【中国警察节】
Don't lose heart.
不要灰心。
This won't be the last time.
这不会是最后一次。
consider me,
考虑我，
【Chinese Police Day】
【中国警察节】
I want to be beaten to death.
我想被打死。
I'm not qualified yet.
我还没有资格。
The professor appears
教授出现了
In the previous game.
在刚才的比赛中。
He went to the same private place
他去了同一个私人地方
as Huang Zicheng.
as Huang Zicheng.
So I think
所以我认为
meet their people
遇见他们的人
It should be the same.
应该是一样的。
Boss Zhang?
张老板？
And this person
而这个人
Be very cautious.
非常谨慎。
Huang Zicheng and Professor
黄子成与教授
Saw him.
见过他。
this means
这意味着
There will be new missions coming soon.
很快就会有新的任务。
I think
我认为
their new mission
他们的新使命
There must be something to do
必须有事可做
with the institute.
与该研究所。
I'm going to report to Director Qin.
我去向秦主任汇报，
See if there is a research institute
看看有没有研究所
Recently in the institute.
最近在研究所。
you pay close attention
你密切关注
Huang Zicheng's game mission.
Huang Zicheng's game mission.
He is very likely
他很有可能
let's go. let's go.
我们走吧。我们走吧。
OK
好的。
Metropark Hotel will host
维景酒店将举办
tomorrow.
明天。
will be led
将被领导
Provided by Gimhae Institute of Biology.
由金海生物研究所提供。
Weijing Hotel that Huang Zicheng entered
Weijing Hotel that Huang Zicheng entered
where
在哪
For hospitality experts.
对于接待专家来说。
【Everyone is responsible for national security】
【国家安全人人有责】
[National Security Bureau in Jinhai]
【驻金海国安局】
Dr. Feng will bring
冯博士将带来
Attend this seminar
参加本次研讨会
and his latest research results.
以及他的最新研究成果。
So is he
他也是
the most influential
最有影响力的
PhD in Genetics
遗传学博士
where is he?
他在哪里？
The flight will arrive at Gimhae Airport
航班将抵达金海机场
30 minutes later.
30分钟后。
Director Qin,
秦主任，
If it is the target of a spy
如果是间谍的目标
This is Dr. Feng,
是冯博士，
I think this is a great opportunity.
我认为这是一个很好的机会。
[National Security Bureau in Jinhai]
【驻金海国安局】
【magnetic levitation】
【磁悬浮】
Dr. Feng?
Dr. Feng?
this way please.
这边请。
Who are you?
你是谁？
We are from the National Security Agency.
我们是国家安全局的。
we want to know something
我们想知道一些事情
About your trip in Gimhae.
关于您在金海的行程。
Can I take a few minutes from you?
我可以占用你几分钟吗？
OK
好的。
Why haven't the game tasks been assigned yet?
为什么游戏任务还没有分配？
Logically speaking,
从逻辑上来说，
They knew we were at the hotel.
他们知道我们在酒店。
The app also has location functionality.
该应用程序还具有定位功能。
what are you waiting for? snort?
你在等什么？哼？
Is the would-be spy impatient?
准间谍不耐烦了？
No.
不。
I am full
我饱了
I am full.
我饱了。
Then stop drinking.
那就别再喝酒了。
Yao Yao.
Yao Yao.
This is me.
这就是我。
Fang Lu.
Fang Lu.
What a coincidence. Why are you here?
真是巧合啊。你为什么在这？
Yes, what a coincidence.
是的，多么巧合啊。
Why are you here?
你怎么也在这里？
Exhibitions of artists I represent
我代理的艺术家的展览
Plans are shown here.
计划在此展示。
So I chose this place.
所以我选择了这个地方。
When did you return to Jinhai?
你什么时候回金海的？
I...
我...
Why don't you introduce him?
你为什么不介绍他呢？
Fang Lu, my friend.
方路，我的朋友。
Huang Zicheng.
Huang Zicheng.
That's it?
就是这样？
what else?
还有什么？
W-we were like
W-我们就像
partner.
伙伴。
Since we are so destined,
既然我们如此有缘，
How about having afternoon tea together?
一起喝下午茶怎么样？
Thanks.
谢谢。
we have something
我们有一些东西
We have other things to do.
我们还有别的事要做。
【Do you accept the mission? 】
【你接受任务吗？】
[confirm cancel]
[确认] [取消]
[Sign in on the 40th floor]
【40楼签到】
Fang, we need to get a room.
方，我们需要开个房间。
Next time you have a private date with her .
下次你和她有私人约会时 。
Open a room? What room?
开房吗？什么房间？
what for?
做什么的？
The mission has come.
使命来了。
ID card. ID card.
身份证。身份证。
Hello.
你好。
check in.
报到。
OK
好的。
Mr. Huang,
Mr. Huang,
The room has been booked in advance.
房间已经提前订好了。
I'll check you in now.
我现在就为您办理入住手续。
please
请
I'm verifying your ID.
我正在验证你的身份证。
Here you go, Mr. Huang.
来了，黄先生。
OK
好的。
miss.
错过。
Is it that man?
是那个男人吗
Your ex-boyfriend?
你的前男友？
An alumnus.
一位校友。
He must be pursuing you, right?
他一定是在追求你吧？
Sort of.
有点。
He looks good.
他看起来不错。
This is your key card.
这是你的房卡。
Room 8022.
8022室。
Go straight and turn right to take the elevator.
直走并右转乘坐电梯。
-Thanks. -Thanks.
-谢谢。-谢谢。
etc.
等等。
Hello?
你好？
Flash delivery?
闪送？
Place it in the lobby on the first floor.
放在一楼大厅。
I will get it.
我会得到它。
Thanks.
谢谢。
let's go.
我们走吧。
[Jinhai Weijing Hotel]
[Jinhai Weijing Hotel]
[Create a model of modern civilized city]
【打造现代文明城市典范】
Hello, there is a Lightning Delivery for you.
你好，有一个闪电配送给你。
Please take it.
请收下。
Thanks.
谢谢。
What's this?
这是什么？
It should be a quest prop.
它应该是一个任务道具。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Will someone come to rob us?
会不会有人来抢劫我们？
I always feel
我总觉得
Someone is watching us.
有人在看着我们。
[Jinhai Weijing Hotel]
[Jinhai Weijing Hotel]
I'm a little scared now.
我现在有点害怕。
This way.
这边走。
8022, go this way.
8022，这边走。
8022。
8022。
8022, this room.
8022，这个房间。
This way.
这边走。
Why do I think this mission is
为什么我觉得这个使命是
Is it any different from the previous one?
和以前的有什么不同吗？
no target.
没有目标。
No prompts.
没有任何提示。
We were just asked to wait.
我们只是被要求等待。
Do you think it's normal?
你觉得正常吗？
Excellent...
出色地...
What is an exception?
什么是异常？
But the game mission
但游戏任务
has been set in advance.
已被提前设定。
What are we waiting for?
我们还在等什么？
Don't worry.
不用担心。
we need to wait
我们需要等待
Until the target appears.
直到目标出现。
All right.
好吧。
OK
好的。
OK, thanks.
好的谢谢。
Hello.
你好。
check in.
报到。
OK
好的。
Check in?
入住吧？
Yes.
是的。
Please take a look at the camera.
请看一下相机。
how?
如何？
Deployment is complete.
部署完成。
Huang Zicheng has checked in
黄子成已打卡
Room 8022
8022室
and his partner.
和他的伙伴。
The girl who left without saying goodbye
不辞而别的女孩
appearing again.
再次出现。
Yes.
是的。
Flash delivery.
闪送。
what is it?
它是什么？
It was registered as a letter.
它被注册为一封信。
There are no surveillance cameras nearby.
附近没有监控摄像头。
Phone number to place order
下订单的电话号码
No real-name information registration has been carried out.
未进行 实名信息注册。
They are meticulous,
他们一丝不苟，
Leave no trace.
不留痕迹。
Doctor Feng, your passport.
冯医生，你的护照。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Your room is ready.
你的房间已经准备好了。
Located on the 80th floor, 8026.
位于80层，8026。
OK Excellent.
好的。出色地。
You can go back to your room and pack your luggage.
就可以回房间 收拾行李了
take a break.
休息一下。
Tonight at six o'clock,
今晚六点，
We will host a welcome reception for you in the hotel restaurant.
我们将在酒店餐厅为您举办欢迎招待会。
6 o'clock.
6点钟。
It's only five o'clock.
现在才五点钟。
Come to my room and have some tea.
到我房间喝点茶吧。
I also brought a gift for Nana.
我还给娜娜带了礼物。
You are so thoughtful.
你想得真周到。
Many thanks.
万分感谢。
let's go.
我们走吧。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Already started?
已经开始了？
Go to room 8026
前往8026室
Get 10 photos of different locations
获取 10 张不同地点的照片
from the computer.
从计算机。
There is an unlocking program in the USB.
USB中有一个解锁程序。
10 photos.
10 张照片。
from different places.
来自不同的地方。
This is a bit difficult.
这有点困难。
not every photo
不是每张照片
There is a background.
有背景。
It's not difficult at all.
一点也不难。
It keeps the following records
它保留了以下记录
Latitude and longitude of location
位置的纬度和经度
Where the photo was taken.
照片拍摄的地方。
That's how I found you.
我就是这样找到你的。
You're kind of smart.
你有点聪明。
so so.
一般般。
This is 8022.
这是8022。
So 8026
所以8026
It should be there.
应该在那儿。
Unlocker
解锁程序
Ready.
准备好了。
right here.
就在这里。
The most important thing now is
现在最重要的是
we do not know
我们不知道
When there is no one in 8026.
当8026没有人的时候。
what if
如果什么
There is always one person,
总有一个人，
There is nothing we can do.
我们没有办法。
Bian,
卞，
This is for your children.
这是给你的孩子的。
I'm so considerate of you
真是为你想得周到
Choose a gift for her.
为她选择礼物。
I remember Nana loved these dolls
我记得娜娜很喜欢这些娃娃
Since childhood.
从小时候起。
These days, how come...
这几天，怎么...
Excellent.
出色地。
Wait a moment.
等一下。
Hello?
你好？
Someone is there.
有人在那里。
[Camera 01]
[相机01]
Dr. Feng went out.
冯医生出去了。
He's out.
他出局了。
I go first.
我先走了。
OK
好的。
Please wait...
请稍等...
Thanks.
谢谢。
please.
请。
action.
行动。
[Camera 01]
[相机01]
[Invade computer]
[入侵计算机]
[The computer was hacked]
【电脑被黑了】
It's too easy.
这太容易了。
[copy and paste]
[复制粘贴]
Huang Zicheng is copying photos.
Huang Zicheng is copying photos.
What picture?
什么照片？
Just some daily photos of Dr. Feng.
只是冯医生的一些日常照片。
Is this his mission?
这就是他的使命吗？
Things shouldn't be that simple.
事情应该没那么简单。
How is this going?
这是怎么回事？
Why is Huang here?
黄怎么来了？
[Jinhai Biological Seminar Schedule]
【金海生物研讨会 日程安排】
Dr. Feng.
Dr. Feng.
Dr. Feng. Dr. F.
冯博士。F.博士
There really is such a person.
还真有这么一个人。
[Geneticist puts in DNA tubes and bottles]
[遗传学家 将DNA管子和瓶子放入]
[Polymerase Chain Reaction Thermal Cycler or Amplifier for Diagnostics ]
[用于诊断的聚合酶链式反应热循环仪 或放大器]
Hello?
你好？
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Hello, Yao Yao.
Hello, Yao Yao.
Something went wrong on this mission.
这次任务出了点问题。
what is it?
它是什么？
Dr. F’s name is Feng Zixiang.
F博士叫冯子祥。
He is a real doctor.
他是一位真正的医生。
He is not an NPC.
他不是NPC。
you do not say?
你不说？
This is just a game mission.
这只是一个游戏任务。
Could it be
难道是
Is the doctor also participating in this game?
那个医生也参加这个游戏？
I'm sending you a photo.
我正在给你发一张照片。
See if it's him.
看看是不是他。
[Huang Zicheng]
[Huang Zicheng]
It looks like it's him.
看来是他了。
Stop the mission now!
立即停止任务！
No why?
没有为什么？
He can't play games.
他不能玩游戏。
[Feng Zixiang]
[Feng Zixiang]
he is a famous
他是一位著名的
PhD in Biology.
生物学博士。
what are you going to do?
你会怎样做？
Abandon the mission.
放弃使命。
you just found out
你刚刚发现
Ten photos.
十张照片。
It's not like
这不像
Important information.
重要信息。
Why 10 photos?
为什么是 10 张照片？
This doesn't make sense.
这没有道理。
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
If this was just a game
如果这只是一个游戏的话
The target will not be Dr. Feng.
目标不会是冯医生。
if this is
如果这是
real espionage,
真正的间谍活动，
It shouldn't just be 10 photos.
它不应该只是10张照片。
Maybe I get it.
也许我明白了。
Huang Zicheng has finished copying.
Huang Zicheng has finished copying.
He only copied a dozen personal photos.
他只复印了十几张 个人照片。
Anything else unusual?
还有什么不寻常的吗？
No.
不。
This doesn't make sense.
这没有道理。
[Suspicious program detected]
[检测到可疑程序]
OK
好的。
[Program is running]
[程序正在运行]
[system error]
[系统错误]
[Cannot be closed during the process]
【过程中无法关闭】
Hey.
嘿。
Did you discover anything?
你有发现什么吗？
There is a problem with the USB.
USB 出现问题。
[Cannot be closed during the process]
[过程中无法关闭]
There is a Trojan horse in the USB.
USB 中有特洛伊木马程序。
activated.
已激活。
Trojan horse program?
特洛伊木马程序？
We were taken advantage of.
我们被利用了。
what do they want
他们想要什么
Not a photo,
不是照片，
But files transferred from computer
但从计算机传输的文件
Via Trojan horse program.
通过特洛伊木马程序。
who are they?
他们是谁？
I also want to know.
我也想知道。
[Tracker program is running]
[追踪器程序正在运行]
Can you find this person?
你能找到这个人吗？
I'm looking for it.
我在找它。
I found it.
我找到了。
He is in the hotel.
他在酒店里。
You don't have to pay attention to them.
你不必留意他们。
Come to my room and wait for me.
到我房间等我。
Something big could happen here.
这里可能会发生大事。
[Tracker program is running]
[追踪器程序正在运行]
[Serving]
[在职的]
A big deal indeed.
确实是一件大事。
[public security]
[公安]
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Are you looking for someone?
你在找人吗？
I'm asking you.
我在问你。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I'm looking for someone.
我正在找人。
spy in bathroom
浴室里的间谍
Stealing information via Trojan horses.
通过特洛伊木马程序窃取信息。
Go find him.
去找他吧。
do not worry about me.
别担心我。
Mind your own business.
管好自己的事吧。
Huang Zicheng, I'm telling you.
Huang Zicheng, I'm telling you.
All you have to do is answer
您只需回答
What am I asking.
我在问什么。
Don't talk about anything else.
别谈别的了。
understand?
理解？
how do you know
你怎么知道
That person is stealing information.
那个人正在窃取信息。
I, I played a game
我、我玩了一个游戏
By playing games.
通过玩游戏。
What mission?
什么使命？
Copy ten photos
复印十张照片
10 photos.
10 张照片。
But later,
但后来，
I checked the USB
我检查了USB
and discovered the Trojan horse program.
并发现了特洛伊木马程序。
they took advantage of me
他们利用了我
Enter Dr. Feng's computer.
进入冯博士的电脑。
They are spies.
他们是间谍。
Say no more.
别再说别的了。
please answer my question.
请回答我的问题。
Who gave you the instructions?
谁给你指示的？
Boss Zhang, in the game.
张老板，在比赛中。
Do you have any other accomplices?
你还有其他同伙吗？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
By the way, I have a partner.
对了，我有一个伙伴。
that girl
那位女孩
Who plays games with me.
谁和我一起玩游戏。
I told you.
我告诉你了。
we were
我们曾经
Just play the game.
只是玩游戏。
We don't know anything else.
我们不知道其他任何事情。
If you just play games
如果你只是玩游戏的话
why did you check
你为什么检查
Trojan horse in USB?
USB 中的特洛伊木马程序？
i just found out
我刚刚发现
there is a problem.
出问题了。
If I had known earlier
如果我早点知道的话
Will I play this game?
我会玩这个游戏吗？
Bro, trust me.
兄弟，相信我。
Go catch them.
去抓住他们吧。
If you catch them,
如果你抓住他们，
you can prove
你可以证明
What I said is true.
我说的是真的。
Answer the officer's questions honestly.
诚实地回答官员的问题。
Does your partner
你的伴侣是否
Any idea what's wrong with the game?
知道游戏中有什么问题吗？
I just told her.
我刚刚告诉她。
What did you tell her?
你告诉她什么了？
I just told her
我刚刚告诉她
There is something wrong with this game.
这个游戏有问题。
someone took advantage of us
有人利用了我们
Enter Dr. Feng's computer.
进入冯博士的电脑。
remember,
记住，
Stop caring about him.
别再关心他了。
Go back now.
现在就回去吧。
Keep playing your game.
继续玩你的游戏。
continue?
继续？
Yes.
是的。
if you do not have
如果你没有
find that person
找到那个人
Didn't meet us here,
并没有在这里遇见我们，
What will you do next?
接下来你会做什么？
Of course I doubt it
那我当然怀疑
They are spies.
他们是间谍。
OK
好的。
Maintain normal reactions,
保持正常反应，
and continue.
并继续。
understand?
理解？
Sort of.
有点。
too late.
太晚了。
Go back now.
现在就回去吧。
Otherwise they will doubt you.
否则他们会怀疑你。
Can you do it?
你可以做到吗？
Yeah, I'll pretend nothing happened
是的，我会假装什么都没发生
in these few minutes.
在这几分钟里。
Go back now.
现在就回去吧。
but...
但...
how?
如何？
Mr. Shen is watching him.
沉先生正在注视着他。
After coming out of the bathroom,
从卫生间出来后，
He returned to the restaurant.
他回到餐厅。
Director Qin.
秦处长。
How is it going?
最近好吗？
As you analyzed,
正如你所分析的，
He stole confidential documents
他偷走了机密文件
We prepared it in the computer.
我们在电脑里准备好的。
he should hand it over
他应该交出
to his superiors.
给他的上级。
Conduct a covert search
进行秘密搜查
Monitor Shi Lei.
对石磊进行监控。
follow the clues
跟随线索
and find his superiors.
并找到他的上级。
Yes.
是的。
A team stayed behind to keep an eye on him.
一队留下来监视他。
Liu, notify the second team.
刘，通知二队。
Get ready for a secret search.
准备好秘密搜查吧。
OK
好的。
Tianyang.
Tianyang.
[Camera 01]
[相机01]
Charge into the room, 8022.
充到房间里，8022。
OK, thanks.
好的谢谢。
What took you so long?
你怎么这么久？
I am anxious.
我很担心。
how?
如何？
Have you found him?
你找到他了吗？
No.
不。
Could it be
难道是
Are you too sensitive?
你太敏感了？
maybe that person
也许那个人
is part of the game.
是游戏的一部分。
impossible.
不可能的。
I guess
我猜测
This is indeed a spy mission.
这确实是一次间谍任务。
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
this game
这个游戏
Completely controlled by spies.
完全被间谍控制。
if this is true
如果这是真的的话
What we experienced abroad
我们在国外经历过的事
Also a spy.
也是间谍。
we got samples
我们拿到了样品
Does it mean we stole confidential information?
意味着我们窃取了机密信息？
No no no.
不不不。
The sample is broken
样品已破碎
Right in front of us.
就在我们面前。
It can't be classified information.
它不可能是机密信息。
you're right.
你说得对。
But there must be something wrong today.
但今天肯定有什么问题。
Did you copy the photo?
你复制照片了吗？
Yes, I deleted them all.
是的，我把它们全部删除了。
Then our mission failed.
然后我们的任务失败了。
at this point,
在此刻，
Are you still thinking about game missions?
你还在考虑 游戏任务吗？
if this is
如果这是
perform espionage missions,
执行间谍任务，
Can we continue this game?
我们可以继续这个游戏吗？
The question is, are you sure?
问题是，你确定吗？
I...
我...
you have not
你还没有
Have you found that person too?
也找到那个人了吗？
No.
不。
I'm just thinking
我只是在想
perhaps
或许
Is this just a game arrangement?
这只是游戏安排？
Computer data theft.
计算机数据盗窃。
Remote hacking.
远程黑客入侵。
If this were game design
如果这就是游戏设计的话
This game is too dangerous.
这个游戏太危险了。
We cannot continue.
我们无法继续。
but...
但...
[Spy Game]
[间谍游戏]
[Submit 10 photos]
[提交10张照片]
The game failed.
游戏失败了。
What can I submit for a task?
我可以为任务提交什么？
Why do you still refuse to give up?
为什么你还是不肯放弃？
certainly!
当然！
Think about it.
想一想。
what have we experienced
我们经历了什么
when we are abroad
当我们在国外的时候
Much scarier than today.
比今天可怕得多。
then,
当时，
We didn't even give up.
我们甚至没有放弃。
hey why are you
嘿，你为什么
More and more cowardly?
越来越懦弱？
Are you not afraid at all?
你一点也不害怕吗？
I'm not scared at all.
我一点也不害怕。
But as you mentioned...
但正如你提到的...
What should we do now?
我们现在应该做什么？
Let's quit the game.
我们退出游戏吧。
We were just scared away
我们只是被吓跑了
In chaos.
混乱中。
we have to
我们必须
Face Mr. Zhang in person
亲自面对张先生
to clarify the matter.
来澄清此事。